Guide to the Washington State Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- WASHINGTON STATE NURSES ASSOCIATION, 1908-1980; RECORD GROUP I
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1918-1977; SERIES V (Box-folder 1/14-1/26, 30/20-30/21, 63/12-63/13, 71/4)
    - Surety Bond, Nell F. Brown, 1930 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Signature authority and insurance records, 1950-1961 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - American Nurses Association retirement policies, 1958 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Group life insurance, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Group life insurance, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Group life insurance, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Seven dread disease insurance program, 1954-1959 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - EDNA B. CUMMINGS RELIEF FUND RECORDS, 1922-1947; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 1/27-1/35)
      - Edna B. Cummings bequest, 1923 (Box-folder 1/27)
      - Policies and beneficiaries, 1932-1938 (Box-folder 1/28)
      - Partial financial statements, 1922-1941 (Box-folder 1/29)
      - Committee and correspondence, 1935-1945 (Box-folder 1/30)
      - Relief application, 1938 (Box-folder 1/31)
      - Case files (part 1 of 4), 1928-1947 (Box-folder 1/32)
      - Case files (part 2 of 4), 1928-1947 (Box-folder 1/33)
      - Case files (part 3 of 4), 1928-1947 (Box-folder 1/34)
      - Case files (part 4 of 4), 1928-1947 (Box-folder 1/35)
    - MAY S. LOOMIS LOAN FUND RECORDS, 1930-1965; SUBSERIES II (Box-folder 1/36-2/5, 13/1-13/4)
      - Ledger, 1931-1941 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Ledger, 1953-1965 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Journal, 1938-1942 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Cash book, 1938-1943 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Loan records (part 1 of 7), 1930-1952 (Box-folder 1/36)
      - Loan records (part 2 of 7), 1930-1952 (Box-folder 1/37)
      - Loan records (part 3 of 7), 1930-1952 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Loan records (part 4 of 7), 1930-1952 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Loan records (part 5 of 7), 1930-1952 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Loan records (part 6 of 7), 1930-1952 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Loan records (part 7 of 7), 1930-1952 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - CONVENTION AND CONFERENCE RECORDS, SERIES VI
    - WASHINGTON STATE NURSES ASSOCIATION CONVENTION RECORDS, 1908-1978; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 2/6-2/21, 19/14-19/25, 30/22-30/58, 37, 41/14-41/18, 53/1-53/16, 63/14-64/13, 71/4-72/4)
      - President's annual address, 1911 (Box-folder 30/22)
      - Convention minutes, 1911-1921 (Box-folder 36/2)
      - Convention minutes, 1918 (Box-folder 30/23)
      - House of Delegates minutes, 1918 (Box-folder 30/24)
      - Convention minutes, 1921 (Box-folder 30/25)
      - Reports to convention, 1922-1936 (Box-folder 71/5)
      - Convention minutes, 1922-1924 (Box-folder 30/26)
      - Convention minutes, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 30/27)
      - Convention minutes, 1926 (Box-folder 30/28)
      - Convention minutes, 1927-1929 (Box-folder 30/29)
      - Convention proceedings: transcript, 1929 (Box-folder 71/6)
      - Convention minutes, 1930 (Box-folder 30/30)
      - Convention minutes, 1931 (Box-folder 30/31)
      - Convention minutes, 1932 (Box-folder 30/32)
      - Convention minutes, 1933 (Box-folder 30/33)
      - Convention minutes, 1934 (Box-folder 30/34)
      - Convention minutes, 1935 (Box-folder 30/35)
      - Convention proceedings, 1936 (Box-folder 71/7)
      - Convention proceedings, 1937 (Box-folder 71/8)
      - Convention program, 1938 (Box-folder 30/36)
      - Convention program, 1939 (Box-folder 30/37)
      - Convention proceedings (part 1 of 2), 1939 (Box-folder 71/9)
      - Convention proceedings (part 2 of 2), 1939 (Box-folder 71/10)
      - Convention proceedings (part 1 of 2), 1940 (Box-folder 71/11)
      - Convention proceedings (part 2 of 2), 1940 (Box-folder 71/12)
      - Convention proceedings, 1942 (Box-folder 71/13)
      - Convention proceedings, 1943 (Box-folder 71/14)
      - Convention proceedings, 1948 (Box-folder 71/15)
      - Convention press clippings, 1931 (Box-folder 30/38)
      - Convention register, 1908-1933 (Box-folder 71/4)
      - Convention registration, 1934-1950 (Box-folder 36/3)
      - Convention registration, 1950 (Box-folder 36/4)
      - Convention scrapbook, 1955 (Box-folder 37)
      - Washington State Nurses Association Presidents' annual addresses, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 30/39)
      - Convention evaluations, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 30/40)
      - Convention invocations, 1949-1964 (Box-folder 30/41)
      - Convention programs, 1931-1970 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Convention proceedings, 1949 (Box-folder 71/16)
      - Convention proceedings, 1950 (Box-folder 71/17)
      - Convention publicity, 1950 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Convention publicity: press clippings, 1950 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Convention records, 1951 (Box-folder 71/18)
      - Convention publicity, 1951 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Convention records, 1952 (Box-folder 71/19)
      - Convention records, 1953 (Box-folder 71/20)
      - Convention: section reports, 1953 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Convention records, 1954 (Box-folder 71/21)
      - Convention: section reports, 1954 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Convention records, 1955 (Box-folder 71/22)
      - Convention: section reports, 1955 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Convention records, 1956 (Box-folder 71/23)
      - Convention: section reports, 1956 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Convention delegates, 1956 (Box-folder 19/14)
      - Convention: section reports, 1957 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Convention records, 1958 (Box-folder 71/24)
      - Convention: section reports, 1958 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Convention publicity, 1958 (Box-folder 41/14)
      - Convention records, 1959 (Box-folder 71/25)
      - Convention: section reports, 1959 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Convention records, 1960 (Box-folder 71/26)
      - Convention: section reports, 1960 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Convention records, 1961 (Box-folder 71/27)
      - Convention: section reports, 1961 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Convention records, 1962 (Box-folder 71/28)
      - Section reports to convention, 1962 (Box-folder 41/15)
      - Convention publicity, 1962 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Convention records, 1963 (Box-folder 71/29)
      - Convention: section reports, 1963 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Convention records, 1964 (Box-folder 71/30)
      - Convention: section reports, 1964 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Convention records (part 1 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 30/42)
      - Convention records (part 2 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 30/43)
      - Convention exhibits, 1962 (Box-folder 30/44)
      - Convention Hostess Committee, 1963 (Box-folder 30/45)
      - Convention program, 1964 (Box-folder 30/46)
      - Convention program, 1964 (Box-folder 41/16)
      - Convention delegates, 1964 (Box-folder 30/47)
      - Convention registration, 1964 (Box-folder 30/48)
      - Tellers and voting chart, 1964 (Box-folder 30/49)
      - Convention follow-up, 1964 (Box-folder 30/50)
      - Convention photographs, 1964 (Box-folder 30/51)
      - Convention records, 1966 (Box-folder 71/31)
      - Convention correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 30/52)
      - Section reports to convention, 1966 (Box-folder 41/17)
      - Convention idea fair, 1966 (Box-folder 30/53)
      - Convention publicity, 1966 (Box-folder 30/54)
      - Convention program planning, 1966 (Box-folder 30/55)
      - Convention exhibitors, 1966 (Box-folder 30/56)
      - Convention delegates, 1966 (Box-folder 30/57)
      - Convention monitors and tellers, 1966 (Box-folder 30/58)
      - Convention records (part 1 of 2), 1968 (Box-folder 72/1)
      - Convention records (part 2 of 2), 1968 (Box-folder 72/2)
      - Continuing education luncheon, 1968 (Box-folder 41/18)
      - Convention records (part 1 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 72/3)
      - Convention records (part 2 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 72/4)
      - Pre-convention board arrangements, 1970 (Box-folder 19/15)
      - Joint section lunch program, 1970 (Box-folder 19/16)
      - Convention correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 19/17)
      - Convention monitors, 1970 (Box-folder 19/18)
      - Convention section files, 1970 (Box-folder 19/19)
      - Convention debates, 1970 (Box-folder 19/20)
      - Delegates, 1970 (Box-folder 19/21)
      - Delegates and tellers, 1970 (Box-folder 19/22)
      - Convention public relations, 1970 (Box-folder 19/23)
      - Resolutions committee, 1970 (Box-folder 19/24)
      - Convention resolutions, 1970 (Box-folder 19/25)
      - Exhibitors, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 53/1)
      - Convention correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 53/2)
      - Convention House of Delegates correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 53/3)
      - Delegates, 1972 (Box-folder 53/4)
      - Convention speakers and guests, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 53/5)
      - Exhibitors, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 53/6)
      - Program: debates, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 53/7)
      - Convention program, 1972 (Box-folder 53/8)
      - Minority Committee luncheon, 1972 (Box-folder 53/9)
      - Printed programs, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 53/10)
      - Monitors, 1972 (Box-folder 53/11)
      - Registration, 1972 (Box-folder 53/12)
      - Voting machines, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 53/13)
      - Voting tellers, 1972 (Box-folder 53/14)
      - Public relations, 1972 (Box-folder 53/15)
      - Convention Resolutions Committee, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/16)
      - Convention correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 63/14)
      - Honorary recognition, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 63/15)
      - House of Delegates, 1973 (Box-folder 63/16)
      - House of Delegates speakers, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 63/17)
      - Call to convention, 1974 (Box-folder 63/18)
      - Exhibits, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 63/19)
      - Exhibitors, 1974 (Box-folder 63/20)
      - Exhibitors working file, 1974 (Box-folder 63/21)
      - Public relations, 1974 (Box-folder 63/22)
      - Registration, 1974 (Box-folder 63/23)
      - Special interest group programs, 1974 (Box-folder 63/24)
      - Voting tellers, 1974 (Box-folder 63/25)
      - Convention correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 63/26)
      - Convention correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 63/27)
      - Awards and honors, 1976 (Box-folder 63/28)
      - Call to convention, 1976 (Box-folder 63/29)
      - Registration, 1976 (Box-folder 63/30)
      - Delegates, 1976 (Box-folder 63/31)
      - Nominees, 1976 (Box-folder 63/32)
      - Exhibitors, 1976 (Box-folder 63/33)
      - Printed programs, 1976 (Box-folder 63/34)
      - Public relations, 1976 (Box-folder 63/35)
      - Tapenotes, Inc., 1976 (Box-folder 63/36)
      - Voting tellers, 1976 (Box-folder 63/37)
      - Convention speakers and programs (part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 63/38)
      - Convention speakers and programs (part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 63/39)
      - Convention correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 63/40)
      - Convention planning, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 63/41)
      - Convention call, 1978 (Box-folder 63/42)
      - Convention participants, 1978 (Box-folder 63/43)
      - Honored guests, 1978 (Box-folder 64/1)
      - Convention speakers, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 64/2)
      - Convention awards, 1978 (Box-folder 64/3)
      - Delegates, 1978 (Box-folder 64/4)
      - House of Delegates (part 1 of 2), 1978 (Box-folder 64/5)
      - House of Delegates (part 2 of 2), 1978 (Box-folder 64/6)
      - Convention programs, 1978 (Box-folder 64/7)
      - Convention monitors, 1978 (Box-folder 64/8)
      - Commission and Committee biennial report to convention, 1978 (Box-folder 64/9)
      - Voting and election procedures, 1978 (Box-folder 64/10)
      - Public relations, 1978 (Box-folder 64/11)
      - Convention exhibitor comments, 1978 (Box-folder 64/12)
      - Convention resource materials, 1968-1976 (Box-folder 64/13)
    - CONFERENCE RECORDS, 1949-1975; SUBSERIES II (Box-folder 2/22, 19/26-20/19, 30/59-31/10, 41/19-42/8, 53/17-53/45, 64/14-64/26)
      - Orientation workshop, 1956 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Conference on the Nurse Shortage, 1963 (Box-folder 30/59)
      - Clinical Conference program materials, 1965 (Box-folder 30/60)
      - Clinical Conference publicity, 1965 (Box-folder 30/61)
      - Presidents' workshop, 1963 (Box-folder 31/1)
      - Presidents' workshop, 1964 (Box-folder 31/2)
      - Conference for District Presidents, 1965 (Box-folder 31/3)
      - General duty workshop, 1955 (Box-folder 31/4)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 31/5)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: minutes and reports, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 31/6)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: evaluations, 1966 (Box-folder 31/7)
      - Head Nurse Conference: sample forms, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 31/8)
      - School health workshop: press clippings, 1958 (Box-folder 31/9)
      - Washington State Congress on Mental Health, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 31/10)
      - Workshops on alcoholism, 1963 (Box-folder 41/19)
      - Nurses' Clinical Conference (part 1 of 2), 1960 (Box-folder 41/20)
      - Nurses' Clinical Conference (part 2 of 2), 1960 (Box-folder 41/21)
      - Nurses' Clinical Conference - copies of talks, 1960 (Box-folder 41/22)
      - Nurses' Clinical Conference (part 1 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 41/23)
      - Nurses' Clinical Conference (part 2 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 41/24)
      - Nurses' Clinical Conference (part 1 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 41/25)
      - Nurses' Clinical Conference (part 2 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 41/26)
      - Cardiac Diet Therapy Workshop, 1960 (Box-folder 41/27)
      - Workshop for District Presidents, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 41/28)
      - General Duty Nurse Workshop, 1949 (Box-folder 41/29)
      - General Duty Nurse Workshop, 1950 (Box-folder 41/30)
      - General Duty Workshop, 1955 (Box-folder 41/31)
      - General Duty and Institutional Nursing Service Administrators Workshop, 1956 (Box-folder 41/32)
      - General Duty Section regional workshops, 1962 (Box-folder 41/33)
      - Workshops on Geriatric Nursing (part 1 of 4), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 41/34)
      - Workshops on Geriatric Nursing (part 2 of 4), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 41/35)
      - Workshops on Geriatric Nursing (part 3 of 4), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 41/36)
      - Workshops on Geriatric Nursing (part 4 of 4), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 41/37)
      - Management Development Workshops, 1961 (Box-folder 42/1)
      - Management Development Workshops, 1962 (Box-folder 42/2)
      - Management Development Workshops, 1963 (Box-folder 42/3)
      - Legislative / Economic Security Workshop, 1968 (Box-folder 42/4)
      - Joint section economic security workshop, 1967 (Box-folder 42/5)
      - Public Health Workshop, 1953 (Box-folder 42/6)
      - Public Relations Workshop, 1951 (Box-folder 42/7)
      - School health workshops, 1955 (Box-folder 42/8)
      - Washington State Nurses' Association Conference for district presidents, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 19/26)
      - American Nurses' Association Conference for physicians and nurses, 1967 (Box-folder 19/27)
      - Washington State Nurses' Association Conference for physicians and nurses, 1970 (Box-folder 19/28)
      - Washington State Nurses' Association regional conferences, 1970 (Box-folder 19/29)
      - Statewide Conference on Revision of the Nurse Practice Act, 1971 (Box-folder 19/30)
      - Washington Women's Highway Safety Conference, 1969 (Box-folder 19/31)
      - American Nurses' Association Conference for State Boards of Nursing, 1966 (Box-folder 19/32)
      - District #2 Board workshop, 1968 (Box-folder 19/33)
      - Legislative / Economic Security Workshop, 1968 (Box-folder 19/34)
      - Nurse Practice Act workshops, 1971 (Box-folder 19/35)
      - Nurse Practice Act seminar, 1972 (Box-folder 19/36)
      - Nurse Practice Act seminar summaries, 1972 (Box-folder 19/37)
      - Nurse Practice Act workshop, 1972 (Box-folder 19/38)
      - Nurse Practice Act: Legislative/PR Task Force, 1972 (Box-folder 19/39)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: minutes, reports and correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 19/40)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: interim projects (part 1 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 19/41)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: interim projects (part 2 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 19/42)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: trainee correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 20/1)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: Alderbrook Inn, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 20/2)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: inquiries, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 20/3)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: photographs, 1966 (Box-folder 20/4)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: photographer and publicity, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 20/5)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: brochures and mailings lists, 1966 (Box-folder 20/6)
      - Rendezvous in Nursing: conference materials, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 20/7)
      - Yardsticks in Nursing Service: correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 20/8)
      - Yardsticks in Nursing Service: correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 20/9)
      - Yardsticks in Nursing Service: faculty, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 20/10)
      - Yardsticks in Nursing Service: interim project reports, c. 1968 (Box-folder 20/11)
      - Yardsticks in Nursing Service: workshop materials, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 20/12)
      - Nurses Clinical Conference, 1967 (Box-folder 20/13)
      - Nurses Clinical Conference: public relations, 1967 (Box-folder 20/14)
      - Nurses Clinical Conference: photographs, 1967 (Box-folder 20/15)
      - Nurses Clinical Conference: public relations, 1969 (Box-folder 20/16)
      - Nurses Clinical Conference: publicity, 1971 (Box-folder 20/17)
      - Head Nurse Conference, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 20/18)
      - Head Nurse Conference: minutes and correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 20/19)
      - Clinical Conference correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 53/17)
      - Regional clinical conferences, 1973 (Box-folder 53/18)
      - North Central Region Clinical Conference: correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/19)
      - North Central Region Clinical Conference: minutes and agenda, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/20)
      - North Central Region Clinical Conference: resource materials, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/21)
      - Northeast Region Clinical Conference: correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 53/22)
      - Northeast Region Clinical Conference: minutes and agenda, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/23)
      - Northeast Region Clinical Conference: resource materials, 1973 (Box-folder 53/24)
      - Southeast Region Clinical Conference: correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/25)
      - Southeast Region Clinical Conference: minutes and agenda, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/26)
      - Southeast Region Clinical Conference: resource materials, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/27)
      - Southwest Region Clinical Conference: correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 53/28)
      - Southwest Region Clinical Conference: minutes and agenda, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/29)
      - Southwest Region Clinical Conference: resource materials, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/30)
      - West Region Clinical Conference: correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 53/31)
      - West Region Clinical Conference: minutes and agenda, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/32)
      - West Region Clinical Conference: resource materials, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 53/33)
      - Gemini training grant application, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 53/34)
      - Inservice education workshops, 1973 (Box-folder 53/35)
      - Inservice education workshops: evaluations, 1973 (Box-folder 53/36)
      - Membership promotion workshops, 1973 (Box-folder 53/37)
      - Physician-Nurse Conference correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 53/38)
      - Physician-Nurse Conference panel participants, 1970 (Box-folder 53/39)
      - Physician-Nurse Conference invitees, 1970 (Box-folder 53/40)
      - Physician-Nurse Conference proceedings, 1970 (Box-folder 53/41)
      - Physician-Nurse Conference correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 53/42)
      - Physician-Nurse Conference, 1972 (Box-folder 53/43)
      - Physician-Nurse Conference invitees, 1972 (Box-folder 53/44)
      - Role Realignment Conference, 1972 (Box-folder 53/45)
      - Conference on Care for the Aged in Nursing Homes, 1974 (Box-folder 64/14)
      - Head Nurse Conference, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 64/15)
      - Yardsticks for Nursing Service: correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 64/16)
      - Yardsticks for Nursing Service: minutes and reports, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 64/17)
      - Yardsticks for Nursing Service session I interim reports, 1969 (Box-folder 64/18)
      - Yardsticks for Nursing Service Conference II interim reports and evaluations, 1969 (Box-folder 64/19)
      - Yardsticks for Nursing Service Conference III interim reports, 1969 (Box-folder 64/20)
      - Coordinating Complexities in Women's Health Care, 1975 (Box-folder 64/21)
      - Role Realignment Conference, 1973 (Box-folder 64/22)
      - Role Realignment Conference planning, 1973 (Box-folder 64/23)
      - Role Realignment Conference 2 (part 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 64/24)
      - Role Realignment Conference 2 (part 2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 64/25)
      - Joint Practice Commission Workshop, 1975 (Box-folder 64/26)
    - AMERICAN NURSES' ASSOCIATION CONVENTION AND CONFERENCE RECORDS, 1919-1978; SUBSERIES III (Box-folder 2/23-2/27, 20/20-20/37, 31/11-31/22, 42/9-42/14, 54/1-54/8, 64/27-65/8, 72/5)
      - Proceedings of the twenty-fourth convention of the American Nurses' Association, 1924 (Box-folder 20/20)
      - Proceedings of the twenty-sixth convention of the American Nurses' Association, 1928 (Box-folder 20/21)
      - American Nurses' Association Proceedings, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 20/22)
      - House of Delegates section reports, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 20/23)
      - House of Delegates section reports, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 20/24)
      - House of Delegates reports, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 20/25)
      - Biennial convention, 1964 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Advisory Council, 1955 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Advisory Council, 1956 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Advisory Council, 1958 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Membership Promotion Conference, 1965 (Box-folder 2/27)
      - American Nurses' Association Regional Conferences on Structure and Bylaws, 1967 (Box-folder 20/26)
      - Convention records, 1968 (Box-folder 20/27)
      - Consents to serve in office, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 20/28)
      - Candidates for office, 1968 (Box-folder 20/29)
      - Resolutions, 1970 (Box-folder 20/30)
      - Convention delegates, 1970 (Box-folder 20/31)
      - Convention materials (part 1 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 20/32)
      - Convention materials (part 2 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 20/33)
      - Candidates for office, 1970 (Box-folder 20/34)
      - Convention breakfast, 1970 (Box-folder 20/35)
      - Convention publicity, 1970 (Box-folder 20/36)
      - Photographs, 1970 (Box-folder 20/37)
      - Seattle preparations for American Nurses' Association convention, 1921 (Box-folder 31/11)
      - Northwest meetings of American Nurses' Association, 1919-1935 (Box-folder 31/12)
      - Northwest Division of American Nurses' Association convention, 1931 (Box-folder 31/13)
      - Northwest Division of American Nurses' Association convention, 1935 (Box-folder 31/14)
      - Northwest Division of American Nurses' Association: convention minutes, 1935 (Box-folder 72/5)
      - American Nurses' Association thirty-second convention. Private Duty Section reports, 1940 (Box-folder 31/15)
      - Proceedings Twenty-Fourth Convention American Nurses' Association, 1944 (Box-folder 31/16)
      - Convention materials and correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 31/17)
      - Convention materials and correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 31/18)
      - Clinical Conference Subcommittee on Psychiatric Nursing, 1960 (Box-folder 31/19)
      - Economic Security Conference, 1968 (Box-folder 31/20)
      - Educational conference for members and professional employees of state boards of nursing, 1965 (Box-folder 31/21)
      - Gerontology and Long-term Illness Conference Group, 1966 (Box-folder 31/22)
      - Biennial convention, 1962 (Box-folder 42/9)